findsounds.com 2018-05-05

# FindSounds - Privacy policy

FindSounds

Search the Web for Sounds 

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which FindSounds.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the http://www.findsounds.com website ("Site").

### Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways in connection with activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

### Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

### How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

### Sharing your personal information

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which FindSounds.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the http://www.findsounds.com website ("Site").

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. 

We may share or sell non-personal information with third parties for marketing or other purposes.

### Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. Doing so will not affect the operation of the site.

### Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. You may learn more about opting out of major ad networks at <https://websitebuilders.com/tools/advertiser-opt-out/>.

### Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics to collect statistics related to the search and retrieval operations provided by Findsounds.com. This is done in order to improve the user experience at findsounds.com. Google Analytics employs the use of HTTP Cookies to be used as a "reminder" of user interactions on the site. and n their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. Google Analytics does not store any personal information about users of FindSounds.com. Read the [Google Analytics privacy document](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html) for more details. 

### Changes to this privacy policy

FindSounds.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. This privacy policy was built [ the web's favorite privacy policy generator](http://privacypolicies.com/).

This document was last updated on June 06, 2017
